export const Data3 = [
    {
      question: 'What are the requirements of students to study in Newzealand?',
      answer: 'To study in New Zealand, a Nepalese student must meet the general requirements for international students, which include to have a vallid passport a student visa and having sufficient funds to support their studies and living costs'
      },
        
    {
      question: 'What is the cost of studying in Newzealand?',
      answer: 'The cost of studying in New Zealand will vary depending on a number of factors, including the type of institution and the program of study. In general, however, international students in New Zealand can expect to pay between NZD 20,000 and NZD 30,000 per year for tuition, plus additional costs for living expenses, travel, and insurance.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Can i stsy in Canada after i graduate?',
      answer: ' Yes, after you graduate from a designated learning institution in Canada, you may be eligible to apply for a post-graduation work permit, which allows you to work in Canada for a period of time that is related to the length of your study program. This can help you gain Canadian work experience and potentially qualify for permanent residence in Canada.'
    },
  
    {
      question: 'Does a Newzealand visa require an interview?',
      answer: 'Once the visa fee has been paid, the applicant will be able to schedule a visa interview with the New Zealand Embassy or Consulate. The visa interview is the final stage of the application procedure, in which one of the consular officers will ask questions in order to assess the applications.'},
        
    {
      question: 'Can i work while studying in Canada?',
      answer: 'Yes, as a study permit holder, you are allowed to work part-time on campus and full-time during scheduled breaks. However, you will need to obtain a work permit in order to work off campus.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Is student life easy in Newzealand?',
      answer: 'The  way of life is enriching and rewarding for international students from all over the world. Canadian universities and colleges are filled with world-class facilities, sports, extracurricular activities, and cultural programs.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Are there scholarships available for international students in Newzealand?',
      answer: ' Yes, there are scholarships available for Nepalese students to study in New Zealand. Some scholarships are offered by the New Zealand government, while others are offered by educational institutions or private organizations.'
    },
    {
        question: 'What are the process for obtaining a student visa extension?',
        answer: 'If you study a postgraduate degree after completing your undergraduate degree, you may be eligible for a Post Study Work Visa that is valid for up to three years.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Does Newzealand accept the gap?',
        answer: ' Even after a ten-year gap, a student can apply for a New Zealand visa if he or she can provide credible information about work experience, studies, and skill set.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Can Nepali students apply for permanent residency in Newzealand after graduating?',
        answer: ' Yes, after graduating from an Canadian educational institution, Nepali students may be eligible to apply for a temporary graduate visa, which allows them to work in Canada for up to four years after graduation. This can provide a pathway to permanent residency in Australia.'
      }


  ];
